A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, photographs, RG 2, 1958-1990 FA499
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Mexico, 323; 0.94 Cubic Feet 2 legal document boxes
  - Mexico - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 323E
    - Guerrero, S. D., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 344)
    - Ilori, F., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 345)
    - Larque - S., F. A., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 346)
    - Larrea Reynoso, Edgar L., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 347)
    - Martinez Legorreta, Omar, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 348)
    - Martinez, S. R., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 349)
    - Miranda J., O., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 350)
    - Oyarzabal T., F., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 351)
    - Perez, M. E., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 352)
    - Rodriguez M., R., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 353)
    - Rodriguez, O., 1971 (Box 8, Folder 354)
    - Rodriguez R., Ramon, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 355)
    - Santos V, S. D. L., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 356)
    - Torres, C. J., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 357)
    - Vera Ferrer, Gabriel A., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 358)
    - Vera G., J., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 359)
  - Mexico - Declinations, 323F
    - Blanco D., V. S., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - Perez G., A., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 361)
- Panama, 327; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Panama
  - Lam, Carols Federico (Box 8, Folder 362)
  - Pitti Quel, Ruben, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 363)
  - Samudio, B. R., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 364)
- Peru, 331; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Peru
  - Peru - General, 331
    - Peru (Box 8, Folder 365)
  - Peru - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 331E
    - Echevarria, R. J. A., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 366)
    - Guillen, L. G., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 367)
    - Postigo Mendivil Rosendo, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 368)
    - Sosa, M., 1967 (Box 8, Folder 369)
  - Peru - Declinations, 331F
    - Sato, A., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 370)
- El Salvador, 333; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  El Salvador
  - El Salvador - General, 333
    - El Salvador (Box 8, Folder 371)
    - Merino A., J., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 372)
  - El Salvador - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 333E
    - Miranda M., S., 1963 (Box 8, Folder 373)
- Dominican Republic, 335; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Dominican Republic
  - Medina G., O., 1982 (Box 8, Folder 374)
- Uruguay, 337; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Uruguay
  - Uruguay - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 337E
    - Drets, Maximo Eduardo - Evangelista Suna de Barone, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 375)
- Venezuela, 339; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Venezuela
  - Caracus Museum of Contemporary Art, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 376)
- England, 401; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  England
  - Dallas, J. F., 1987 (Box 8, Folder 377)
  - Kings College Hospital, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 378)
  - Lambretta - Trojan Company, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 379)
  - Lugwig Foundation, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 380)
  - Management Agricultural Research (Development and Research), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 381)
  - Tropical Products Institute, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 382)
  - University of Cambridge (Nutrition), 1972 (Box 8, Folder 383)
  - Watkins, W., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 383A)
- Ireland, 403; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Ireland
  - Ireland - General, 403
    - Trinity College (Dublin Lyons), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 384)
  - Ireland - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 403D
    - Agriculture, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 385)
  - Ireland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 403E
    - Simpson, D. I. M., 1964 (Box 8, Folder 386)
- Australia, 410; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Australia
  - Australia - General, 410
    - Finlay, K. W., 1978 (Box 8, Folder 387)
    - National Science Center, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 388)
    - University of Sydney (Dept. Of Obstetrics), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 389)
    - Van Cleef Foundation (Bradley), 1961 (Box 8, Folder 390)
    - University of New South Wales, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 391)
  - Australia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 410E
    - Mackaness, George B, 1959 (Box 8, Folder 392)
- Caribbean Region and Central America, 420; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Caribbean Area; Central America
  - Caribbean Region and Central America - General, 420
    - Confederation of Central American Universities, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 393)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 420A
    - Caribbean Committee for Bilharzia Research, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 394)
- British Honduras, 425; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Belize
  - British Honduras/Belize (Replication of Technoserve) (Box 9, Folder 395)
- Canada, 427; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Canada
  - Canada - General, 427
    - Family Planning Federation of Canada, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 396)
    - McMaster University, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 397)
    - Montreal Opera Company, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 398)
  - Canada - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 427A
    - McGill University Medical School, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 399)
- Jamaica, 437; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Jamaica
  - University College of the West Indies, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 400)
- Trinidad, 451; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Trinidad and Tobago
  - Trinidad - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 451E
    - Delpeche, K. A., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 401)
- India, 464; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  India
  - India - General, 464
    - Balwant Rajput College, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - Chaudhuri, D., 1969 (Box 9, Folder 403)
    - Indian (A-Z), 1961 (Box 9, Folder 404)
    - Indian Agricultural Research Institute (Santhanam), 1966 (Box 9, Folder 405)
    - Menta, Y. R., 1968 (Box 9, Folder 406)
    - Vaidya, Antubhai, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 407)
  - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 464E
    - Kasturba Medical College, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 408)
    - Bandyopadhyay, K. G., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 409)
    - Bhaktaviziam, Aleyamma, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 410)
    - Dikshit, Dr. S. K., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 411)
    - Dorai Raj, B.S., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 411A)
    - Ramarao, Baichwal Pranesh, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 412)
    - Sethurama, S. V., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 413)
    - Shrestha, R. B., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 414)
    - Singh, Sher, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 415)
- Pakistan, 465; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Pakistan
  - Pakistan - General, 465
    - Syed, A. H., 1958 (Box 9, Folder 416)
  - Pakistan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 465E
    - University of Karachi (Mahmood), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 417)
    - Ahmed, N., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 418)
    - Khan, Razia, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 419)
- Iraq, 470; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Iraq
  - Al-Hikma University, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 420)
- Kenya, 476; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Kenya
  - Kenya - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 476E
    - Yousiph, Y el, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 421)
    - Asingo, N., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 425)
    - Bonuke, J. N., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 426)
    - Cege, Peter, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 427)
    - Mohamed, Abdul Kader Abdu, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 428)
    - Mukasa, S., 1967 (Box 9, Folder 429)
    - Muthaka, P. W., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 430)
    - Onyango, I. A., 1979 (Box 9, Folder 431)
  - Kenya - General, 476
    - Kenya (Box 9, Folder 424)
  - Kenya - Declinations, 476F
    - Odhiambo, T. R., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 432)
- Malaysia, 473; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Malaysia
  - Song, L. S. P., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 422)
- Africa, 475; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Africa
  - Africa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 475D
    - Agriculture, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 423)
- Rwanda, 477; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Rwanda
  - Rwanda (Box 9, Folder 433)
  - University College of Usumbura, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 434)
- Rhodesia, 483; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Zimbabwe
  - Private Game Reserve and Research, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 435)
- South Africa Region, 487; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Africa, Southern
  - University of Witwatersrand (Sutton), 1958 (Box 9, Folder 436)
- Uganda, 492; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Uganda
  - Uganda - General, 492
    - Bitarabeho, P., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 437)
    - Kateshumbwa, A. B., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 438)
  - Uganda - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 492E
    - Baliddawa, C. W. (Box 9, Folder 439)
    - Gurnah, A. M., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 440)
    - Kakoza, J., 1967 (Box 9, Folder 441)
    - Katorobo, James, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 442)
    - Luboobi, L. S., 1971 (Box 9, Folder 443)
    - Luguijjo, S. Eriabu, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 444)
    - Mawanje, J., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 445)
    - Mayega, Joseph V., 1968 (Box 9, Folder 446)
    - Nyiira, Z. M., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 447)
    - Osiru, D. S. O., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 448)
    - Sabiiti, E. N., 1981 (Box 9, Folder 449)
- Sudan, 494; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Sudan
  - Sudan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 494E
    - Ayoub, Suliman Tatta, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 450)
    - Morgan, Joseph Awad, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 451)
    - Mustafa, I. D., 1967 (Box 9, Folder 452)
- West Africa, 495; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Africa, West
  - Administration, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 453)
  - Niger, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 454)
  - Organization of African Unity Research Committee, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 455)
- Ghana, 496; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Ghana
  - Ghana (Box 9, Folder 456)
  - Institute of Tropical Medicine and Encemic Diseases, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 457)
- Nigeria, 497; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Nigeria
  - Nigeria - General, 497
    - Amuka, Samson Oruru, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 458)
    - Education (JELF), 1963 (Box 9, Folder 459)
    - P. Chukwwemeka Eze, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 460)
    - University of Ibanan (Plant Virology) And (Swine Insemination), 1972 (Box 9, Folder 461)
  - Nigeria - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 497E
    - University of Veterinary Medicine (Ahmadu Bella) (Box 9, Folder 462)
    - Adenikinju, S. A., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 463)
    - Akpata, R. I., 1963 (Box 9, Folder 464)
    - Aleyideino, Edwardo, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 465)
    - Lavender, W., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 466)
    - Momah, C. K., 1970 (Box 9, Folder 467)
    - Nwana, I. E., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 468)
    - Odumuye, S., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 469)
    - Ogionwo, W. W., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 470)
    - Ojedokun, O., 1965 (Box 9, Folder 471)
    - Okoye, Barnabas Ikechukima, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 472)
    - Osunkay, Babatunde, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 473)
    - Owualah, E. N., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 474)
    - Smith, O. A., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 475)
  - Nigeria - Declinations, 497F
    - Ajie, E. O., 1963 (Box 9, Folder 476)
    - Ojemen, A. A., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 477)
- Sierra Leone, 499; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Sierra Leone
  - Sierra Leone - Medical Sciences, 499A
    - University College of Sierra Leone (Medical School), 1962 (Box 9, Folder 478)
  - Sierra Leone - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 499E
    - Kandeh, H. B. S., 1984 (Box 9, Folder 479)
- France, 500; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  France
  - Sister Louise Walter, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 480)
  - Maison de la Culture Andre Malraux Reims, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 481)
- Vietnam, 509; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Vietnam
  - Truong Phuoc Nien, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 482)
- Asia, 600; 0.47 Cubic Feet
  Asia
  - Fisheries, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 483)
- China, 601; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  China
  - China - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 601D
    - Agriculture, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 486)
  - China - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 601E
    - Cheng Wei-Zhong, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 487)
  - Chinese Academy of Agriculture Sciences (Rice Biotechnology) (Box 10, Folder 484)
  - Xu, Kai, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 485)
- Taiwan, 605; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Taiwan
  - Asian Vegetable Development Center, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 488)
  - Fu Jen University (Arens), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 489)
  - Yen, Sylvia Chih Ying, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 490)
- Japan, 609; 0.47 Cubic Feet
  Japan
  - Japan - General, 609
    - Doshisha University (Hata), 1961 (Box 10, Folder 491)
    - Council for the Promotion of Photography (Box 10, Folder 492)
    - Fujita, H., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 493)
    - Hosokawa, Akira, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 494)
    - Ishii, M., 1958 (Box 10, Folder 495)
    - Kametaka, M., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 496)
    - Kinki University, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 497)
    - Kyoto University (Medical Library), 1958 (Box 10, Folder 498)
    - Kyushi University (Agriculture), 1965 (Box 10, Folder 499)
    - Murata, Kiyoaki, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 500)
    - Nagoya City University (Maruchi), 1964 (Box 10, Folder 501)
    - Nagoya University (Kitagawa), 1962 (Box 10, Folder 502)
    - Nakamura, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 503)
    - National Institute of Afrobiological Resources (Box 10, Folder 504)
    - National Institute of Agricultural Science (Tokyo), 1967 (Box 10, Folder 505)
    - Noda, T., 1959 (Box 10, Folder 506)
    - Ohtaka, M., 1960 (Box 10, Folder 507)
    - Osaka Bargemen's Children's Home, 1958 (Box 10, Folder 508)
    - Sanjo, M., 1962 (Box 10, Folder 509)
    - Sapporo Medical College, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 510)
    - Suzuki, S., 1965 (Box 10, Folder 511)
    - Tokoyo Women's University (Saito), 1962 (Box 10, Folder 512)
  - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 609E
    - Isozaki, Arata, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 513)
    - Kudo, A., 1959 (Box 10, Folder 514)
    - Okuhara, E., 1959 (Box 10, Folder 515)
    - Watanabe, S., 1961 (Box 10, Folder 516)
  - Japan - Declinations, 609F
    - Japan Maha Bodhi Society, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 517)
- Korea, 613; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Korea
  - Korea - General, 613
    - International Culture Research Center, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 518)
    - Korean Research Institute for Dramatic Arts, Inc., 1966 (Box 10, Folder 519)
    - Park, K. W., 1958 (Box 10, Folder 520)
  - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 613E
    - OH, S. J., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 521)
- Thailand, 617; 0.94 Cubic Feet 2 legal document boxes
  Thailand
  - Thailand - General, 617
    - Chatthip, N., 1964 (Box 10, Folder 522)
    - Chulabhorn, Princess, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 523)
    - Kandeporn, Ounjaichen, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 524)
    - Kasetsart University, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 525)
    - Kiertsackdi, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 526)
    - Krit, M., 1962 (Box 10, Folder 527)
    - Mahidol University (Thalassemias), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 528)
    - Tavat, L., 1962 (Box 10, Folder 529)
  - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 617E
    - Amara, B., 1972 (Box 10, Folder 530)
    - Anan, Supawan, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 531)
    - Anonda, A., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 532)
    - Apirak, T., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 533)
    - Arkom, S., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 534)
    - Arporn, T., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 535)
    - Bhatra, P., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 536)
    - Boonlert, B., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 537)
    - Boonyatharakul, W., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 538)
    - Chai, P., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 539)
    - Chalintorn, N., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 540)
    - Chalerm, M., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 541)
    - Chamien, B., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 542)
    - Chamond, A., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 543)
    - Chaturongakul, Songphol, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 544)
    - Choosri, Bumrungpruik, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 545)
    - Decha, C., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 546)
    - Hirunnetra, Chaleo, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 547)
    - Intrachond, P., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 548)
    - Kamol, S. (Box 10, Folder 549)
    - Kantasewi, Niphon, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 550)
    - Khanjanapaj, L., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 551)
    - Khemark, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 552)
    - Khumgliang, P., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 553)
    - Kootin, S., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 554)
    - Kraisorn, K., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 555)
    - Kulthon, T., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 556)
    - Luansark, W., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 557)
    - Manit, L., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 558)
    - Marisa, C., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 559)
    - Mongkol, S., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 560)
    - Montree, Borisutdhi, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 561)
    - Nati, Nilnophakoon, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 562)
    - Ngamchuen, K., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 563)
    - Niyom, J., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 564)
    - Niyomyaht (Swetwatna), Sawong, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 565)
    - Paitoon, S., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 566)
    - Panas, S., 1968 (Box 10, Folder 567)
    - Panee, B., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 568)
    - Piroj, V., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 569)
    - Pongumphai, S., 1967 (Box 10, Folder 570)
    - Pornpimol, C., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 571)
    - Prabhant, K., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 572)
    - Prakong, I., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 573)
    - Prason, P., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 574)
    - Rainan, A., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 575)
    - Ratisoontorm, P., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 576)
    - Rujira, P. S., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 577)
    - Samart, Meekanguan, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 578)
    - Sampham, V., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 579)
    - Sanit, A., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 580)
    - Sauan, P., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 581)
    - Senavong, C., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 582)
    - Siripun, S., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 583)
    - Smarn, T., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 584)
    - Somporn, S., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 585)
    - Somjate, J., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 585A)
    - Suchitra, V., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 586)
    - Sujin, S., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 587)
    - Sukit, V., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 588)
    - Sumpoonworawanit, T., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 589)
    - Suphan, T., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 590)
    - Surartik, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 591)
    - Suri, V., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 592)
    - Suvit, P., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 593)
    - Thasayanon, Wannasiri, 1966 (Box 11, Folder 594)
    - Tiamjai, K., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 595)
    - Tongyot, A., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 596)
    - Tusanee, N., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 597)
    - Vadhanasuka, S., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 598)
    - Varunyaront, A., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 599)
    - Vichit, Y., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 600)
    - Viyada, K., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 601)
    - Wilaiwan, W., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 602)
  - Thailand - Social Sciences, 617S
    Social sciences
    - University of Thammas at Economics, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 603)
    - Amiruddin, O. K., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 604)
    - Sytsma, M., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 605)
- Holland, 650; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Netherlands
  - University of Utrecht (Van Lennep, D. J.), 1959 (Box 11, Folder 606)
- Indonesia, 652; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Indonesia
  - Indonesia - General, 652
    - Liauw, K. H., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 607)
    - Lim Tijoan Hok, S., 1961 (Box 11, Folder 608)
    - Oemarjati Slamet, B. S., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 609)
    - Purnadi, P., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 610)
    - Santoso, M. V., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 611)
    - Ubad Art Museum, 1963 (Box 11, Folder 612)
  - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 652E
    - Harsono, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 613)
    - Kamiso, I., 1976 (Box 11, Folder 614)
    - Rahardjo, M., 1974 (Box 11, Folder 615)
    - Soewadi, M., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 616)
    - Utomo, W. T., 1974 (Box 11, Folder 617)
- Aruba (Netherlands Antilles), 658; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Aruba
  - Aruba - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 658E
    - Pole, W. M., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 618)
- Ethiopia, 701; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Ethiopia
  - Ethiopia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 701E
    - Kidane-Mariam, Haile-Michael, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 619)
- Belgium, 707; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Belgium
  - Belgium - General, 707
    - Association for the Promotion of Patrimony, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 620)
    - Brecx, Paul, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 621)
    - Institute Royal du Patuimoine Artistique, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 622)
    - Theatre Inpopulaire, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 623)
  - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 707E
    - Morissen, S. L., 1963 (Box 11, Folder 624)
- Zaire, 709; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Congo (Democratic Republic)
  - Zaire - General, 709
    - Zaire Republic (Box 11, Folder 625)
  - Zaire - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 709E
    - Kayitenkore, E., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 626)
    - Lukau-Nkodi, M., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 627)
    - Luvwezo, M., 1977 (Box 11, Folder 628)
    - Malembe, P., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 629)
    - Maphana, M. N., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 630)
- Germany, 717; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Germany
  - Jander, Rudolf, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 631)
  - Jobst, Ursula, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 632)
- Tanzania, 723; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Tanzania
  - Tanzania - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 723E
    - Besha, M. P., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 633)
    - Kaduma, I. M., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 634)
    - Kamuzora, H. L., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 635)
    - Kayage, F. J., 1975 (Box 11, Folder 636)
    - Kotta, J. R., 1965 (Box 11, Folder 637)
    - Machunda, Z. B., 1979 (Box 11, Folder 638)
    - Mwita, S. W., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 639)
    - Sipuka, Frank, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 640)
- Zambia, 724; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Zambia
  - University of Zambia, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 641)
- Hungary, 750; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Hungary
  - National Institute of Hygiene, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 642)
- Italy, 751; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Italy
  - American Academy in Rome, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 643)
  - Centro di Ricerca e Documentazione, 1982 (Box 11, Folder 644)
  - Rossellini, R., 1972 (Box 11, Folder 645)
  - University of Florence (Law School), 1958 (Box 11, Folder 646)
- Liberia, 759; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Liberia
  - Liberia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 759D
    - University of Liberia (Agriculture), 1965 (Box 11, Folder 647)
- Portugal, 773; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Portugal
  - Portugal - General, 773
    - Roer, M. (Box 11, Folder 648)
  - Portugal - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 773D
    - Agriculture, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 649)
- Russia, 785; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Soviet Union
  - Moscow Poliomylistis and Viril Enceohalitis Institute, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 650)
- Finland, 787; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Finland
  - Pesola, Vilho A., 1967 (Box 11, Folder 651)
- Poland, 789; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Poland
  - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 789E
    - Kudera, M., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 652)
    - Kozieradzka, Barbara, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 653)
    - Szczepkowski, T. W., 1962 (Box 11, Folder 654)
    - Zurzycka, A., 1958 (Box 11, Folder 655)
    - Zygient, Z., 1959 (Box 11, Folder 656)
- Sweden, 800; 0.47 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box
  Sweden
  - Holmgren, Uno, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 657)
  - University of Uppsala Lindahl, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 658)
- Turkey, 805; 0.71 Cubic Feet 1 legal document box and 1 half-legal document box
  Turkey
  - Turkey - General, 805
    - Vatasever, A., 1966 (Box 11, Folder 659)
    - Yahman, T., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 660)
  - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 805E
    - Attay, Fahri, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 661)
    - Onat, Sigdem Selisik, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 662)
    - Orberk, T., 1958 (Box 12, Folder 663)
    - Solen, Polak, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 664)
    - Yilmaz, B., 1978 (Box 12, Folder 665)
- Jordan, 816; 0.24 Cubic Feet 1 half-legal document box
  Jordan
  - Jordan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 816E
    - Ayyash, Adil, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 666)
    - Kamawi, S. M. A., 1960 (Box 12, Folder 667)
- Saudi Arabia and Oman, 817; 0.24 Cubic Feet 1 half-legal document box
  Saudi Arabia; Oman
  - King Faisal Foundation, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 668)
- Israel, 825; 0.24 Cubic Feet 1 half-legal document box
  Israel
  - Israel - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 825D
    - Agriculture - Shlomi, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 669)
- Lebanon, 833; 0.24 Cubic Feet 1 half-legal document box
  Lebanon
  - Lebanon - General, 833
    - Khatchadourian, Haig, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 670)
  - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 833E
    - Habashi, R., 1959 (Box 12, Folder 671)